Guide to the Office of the Secretary, Yale University, Annual Reports Submitted to the President
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Annual reports for departments and schools, 1994-2000; Accession 2002-A-193
  - Archaeological Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Architecture, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Berkeley College, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Biology -Molecular, Cellular, and Dev., 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - British Art Center, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - British Art Center, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Bush Center for Child Development, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Calhoun College, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Cell and Molecular Physiology, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Cell Biology, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Center for Study of Amer Art, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Chemistry, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Child Study Center, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Comparative Literature, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Comparative Medicine, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Computer Science, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Conn Mental Health Center, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Davenport College, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Dermatology, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Diagnostic Radiology, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Drama School, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - East Asian Lang/Lit, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Economics, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - English, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Ezra Stiles College, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - French, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Genetics, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Geology/Geophysics, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - History of Art, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - History of Medicine, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Immunobiology, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Institute for Biospheric Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Inst of Sacred Music, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Inst Soc/Policy Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - International/Area Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - International/Area Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - International Security, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Italian, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Jon Edwards College, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Judaic Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Laboratory Medicine, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Philosophy, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Religious Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Sociology, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Statistics, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Teacher's Prep, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Therapeutic Radiology, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Timothy Dwight College, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Trumbull College, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - University Librarian, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - University Librarian, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - University Librarian, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Yale College, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Yale Health Services, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Epidemiology and Pub Health, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Ezra Stiles College, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - History of Medicine, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Law School, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Law School, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Management School, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Mathematics, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Medical School, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Medieval Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Molecular Biophysics/Biochemistry, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Music Dept, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Near Eastern Lang/Lit, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Neurology, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Nursing School, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Ophthalmology, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Pathology, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Peabody Museum, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Pediatrics, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Pharmacology, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Physics, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Political Science, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - Psychiatry, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Psychology, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Religious Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Renaissance Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Slavic Lang/Literature, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Sociology, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Spanish/Portuguese, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Statistics, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Statistics, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Surgery, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Teacher Prep Program, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Therapeutic Radiology, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Trumbull College, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - University Health Services, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - University Librarian, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - Visitor Information, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - Yale Psychiatric Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Hard cover books (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Yale Athletics, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Yale Athletics, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Yale Athletics, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Anesthesiology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Anthropology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Archaeological Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Architecture, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Biology -Molecular, Cellular, and Dev., 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Boyer Center Molecular Medicine, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - British Art Center, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Bush Center Child Development, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Calhoun College, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Child Study Center, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Comparative Literature, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Comparative Medicine, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Computer Science, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Davenport College, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Diagnostic Radiology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Divinity School, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - East Asian Lang/Literature, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Economic Growth Center, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Economics, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - English, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Epidemiology and Pub Health, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Genetics, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Immunobiology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Institute for Biospheric Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Inst of Sacred Music, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Inst Soc/Policy Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - International/Area Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - International Security, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Jon Edwards College, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Laboratory Medicine, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Management School, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Molecular Biophysics/Biochemistry, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Neurology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Nursing School, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Ophthalmology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Orthopaedics and Rehab, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Peabody Museum, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Pharmacology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Philosophy, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Physics, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Physics, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Political Science, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Psychiatry, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Psychology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Saybrook College, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Slavic Lang/Lit, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Sociology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Surgery, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Therapeutic Radiology, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Trumbull College, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - University Librarian, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Yale College, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - Henry Fellowship, 1989-1999 (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - miscellaneous memos, 1981 October (Box 8, Folder 245)
  - Educational Opportunity Fund (Box 8, Folder 246)
  - Planning issues for Development (Box 8, Folder 247)
  - Ad Hoc Committee Faculty Appointments (Box 8, Folder 248)
  - Security Briefing Paper, 1981 June (Box 8, Folder 249)
  - Finance and Administration (Box 8, Folder 250)
  - Constitution of Communications Board of Yale University (Box 8, Folder 251)
  - Yale Alumni Publications Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 252)
  - Master Environmental Studies Program, 1981 April (Box 8, Folder 253)
  - Security Briefing Paper (Box 8, Folder 254)
  - The State of Undergraduate Student Governance, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 255)
  - Resolution of New Haven Board of Alderman requesting low, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 256)
  - Income housing for Yale University. (Box 8, Folder 257)
  - Miscellaneous Corporation Committee Minutes, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 258)
  - Miscellaneous Corporation Committee Minutes, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 259)
  - Proposed Amendments Bylaws, 1988 October (Box 8, Folder 260)
  - Corporation Mailing, 1988 December (Box 8, Folder 261)
  - Book, "Rebuilding Yale-the next five years" (Box 8, Folder 262)
  - Corporation Mailing, 1989 January (Box 8, Folder 263)
  - Corporation Mailing, 1989 March (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Corporation Finance gift revenue, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Non-endowment investment income (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Grants and Contracts Review (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Tuition Income (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Major Revenue Sources (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Corporation Committee Institutional Policy Minutes, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Memo from Deborah L. Rhode, Statement on Proxy Resolutions (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Corporation Committee Trusteeship, 1996 December (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Agendas (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Audit Committee Minutes (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Saybrook College (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Slavic Language/ Literature (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Sociology (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Theraputic Radiology (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Timothy Dwight College (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - University Librarian (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Yale College (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Yale Institute of Biospheric Studies (Box 8, Folder 282)
- Annual reports, 2000-2001; Accession 2004-A-163
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  - American Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anesthesiology, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anthropology, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Architecture, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Branford, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bush, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Calhoun, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chemistry, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Comparative Lit., 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Comparative Med., 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Computer Science, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dept. of History, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Divinity, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Drama, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - East Asian Language, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ecology, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Electrical Engineering, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - English, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ezra Stiles, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - French, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Graduate School, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - International and Area Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Laboratory Medicine, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Mathematics, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - MB and B, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Molecular Cellular, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Music Dept., 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Near Eastern, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Neurology, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Neurosurgery, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Nursing, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - OB -GYN, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Ophthalmology, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Philosophy, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Physics, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Political Science, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Psychiatry, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Psychology, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Public Health, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Religious Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - S.O.M., 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Sociology, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Social Policy Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Spanish and Portuguese, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Surgery, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Silliman, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Trumbull, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Yale Art Gallery, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Yale College, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Yale Institute Biospheric Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Yale University Library, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Annual reports, 2009-2016; Accession 2018-A-053
  Restricted until January 1, 2052.
  - School of Architecture, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Art Gallery, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arthur Liman Public Interest Program, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Center for British Art, 2009-2015 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Center for International and Professional Experience, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Science, 2009-2015 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Sacred Music, 2012-2015 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory Medicine, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Yale Law School Annual Reports of Giving, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - School of Management, 2009-2012 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - School of Nursing, 2009-2015 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Department of Molecular, Cellular, and Developmental Biology, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Peabody Museum of Natural History, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Department of Political Science, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Richard U. Light Fellowship Program, 2009-2015 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Yale Summer Session, 2011-2016 (Box 3, Folder 3)